http://www.printedpens.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

PensPencils & CrayonsHighlighters & MarkersPresentation CasesAccessoriesPierre Cardin
TypeRollerballFountain PenCapped BallpenPush-Button BallpenStickpenTwist-Action BallpenMulti-FunctionMini PenSpecialist PenGel PensCapped Multi-FunctionCap-Action BallpenCapless RollerPush-Button Multifunction BallpenCapless BallpenTwist Action Multi-FunctionDesktop PenFelt Tip PenMaterialPlastic PensMetal PensWooden PensEco-FriendlyCarbon Fibre PensBranding MethodFull Colour BrandingLaser EngravedSpot ColourExpress Service24 Hour Express3 Day ExpressSame-Day Express48 Hour ExpressEco-FriendlyTypeMechanical PencilCrayonsPencil With EraserPencil Without EraserColouring Pencil SetPush-Button Mech PencilPlastic PencilMaterialWooden PencilsPlastic PencilsMetal PencilsEco-FriendlyMetal Pencils & CrayonsSoya CrayonsBranding MethodFull Colour BrandingLaser EngravedSpot ColourExpress Service24 Hour Express3 Day ExpressNo Minimum OrderEco-FriendlyTypeHighlighterMarker PensDry Wipe MarkerPermanent MarkerUV Marker PensBallpen/HighlighterBranding MethodFull Colour BrandingSpot ColourExpress Service24 Hour Express3 Day ExpressNo Minimum Order QuantityEco-FriendlyTypePresentation TubeGift Box - Single or DoublePresentation PouchGift Box - SingleGift Box - DoubleMaterialPlastic Presentation CasesCard Presentation CasesCard/Plastic Presentation CasesMetal Presentation CasesWood Presentation CasesBranding MethodMaterialRubber AccessoriesPlastic AccessoriesMetal AccessoriesTypeEraserClipPencil SharpenerPen HolderPen SetBranding MethodBallpoint PensRollersFountainsPresentation Boxes
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how BOSTON Promotional Gifts UK uses and protects any information that you give BOSTON Promotional Gifts UK when you use this website. BOSTON Promotional Gifts UK is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. BOSTON Promotional Gifts UK may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
UK Call Recording Legal Compliance
The following FAQ is intended to summarise the key points in the legal and regulatory environment in regard to call recording in the UK. It is not possible to provide comprehensive detail of all legislation here.
For what reasons can I record my customer’s calls?
The Lawful Business Practice [LBP] Regulations specify conditions upon which calls may be recorded. These are to:
Provide evidence of a business transaction.
Ensure that a business complies with regulatory procedures.
See that quality standards or targets are being met in the interests of national security.
Prevent or detect crime to investigate the unauthorised use of a telecom system.
Secure the effective operation of the telecom system.
The LBR regulations can be found on the DTI website
Do I need consent from my callers to record calls?
No, provided the recording is to meet one of the above conditions and you are not intending to make the recording available to a third party. If you are recording for any other purpose, such as marketing or market research, you will need consent from the third party. If you are intending to make the recordings available to a third party, then you must make every reasonable effort to inform all parties to a telephone conversation that it may or will be recorded.
How do I advise callers that they may be recorded?
The particular means by which you choose to do this are not specified. Acceptable options, depending on circumstances, might include warning tones, pre-recorded messages, spoken warnings by the operator or written warnings included in publicity material, telephone directories, contracts, terms of business, etc. It may not always be possible to warn first-time callers with whom you have had no previous contact but what is important is that you have a systematic procedure in place which provides the necessary information wherever this is a realistic possibility." In these cases call recording is authorized on the basis that there is reasonable grounds to believe the caller has consented.
Do I need to notify my employees that calls are recorded?
Yes. Businesses can monitor, but not record, phone calls to see whether they are relevant to the business (ie open an employee's voicemail or mailbox systems while they are away to see if there are any business communications stored there). Companies and organisations that routinely record telephone calls must ensure that their employees are able to make personal calls that are not also recorded under the same system. Staff must also be made aware that personal conversations could be recorded on their telephone and must have access to a separate telephone on the premises where they can make and receive personal calls that are not recorded.
What is the relevant legislation?
Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 ("RIPA") An interception is only lawfully carried out if one of the following applies
(i) The person intercepting the call has reasonable grounds for believing that it has the consent of both the caller and the intended recipient of the call to intercept; or
(ii) The interception is carried out by a business in compliance with the Lawful Business Practice Regulations (see below.)
The Telecommunications (Lawful Business Practice) (Interception of Communications) Regulations 2000 (the "Regulations") Interception is authorised if the business which is intercepting the call has made all reasonable effort to inform potential users that their communications may be intercepted, and the interception is then carried out:
To establish the existence of facts (eg to evidence a business transaction);
To assess or demonstrate that standards "which ought to be achieved" are achieved (eg quality control and training standards);
To prevent or detect a crime, or for purposes of national security;
To assess compliance with regulatory practices or procedures applicable to the business;
To investigate or detect unauthorised use of the communications system; or
To determine whether communications are relevant to the system controller’s business.
The Data Protection Act 1998 ("DPA") Recording (and use of recordings) where you can determine the identity of either party to the call, either directly from the recording or from other information, would require you to first:
Have informed that party how the recording would be used;
Obtain consent for the recording to take place (This may be implied from the fact that the customer has been notified and not objected, but you should obtain explicit consent if the call reveals any information classified as sensitive by the DPA, ie details of race/ethnic background, political opinion, religion, trade union membership, physical/mental health, sexual life, offences committed or legal proceeding bought.)
The obligations in relation to processing of that data also apply, so that the data must be kept for longer than necessary, under secure conditions and must be accessible to the customer at their request.
The Employment Practices, Data Protection Code The code states that employees should be informed about any monitoring of their calls and that their consent should be obtained (as required under the DPA.)
Human Rights Act 1998 The Act provides that "everyone has the right to respect for his private life and family life, his home and his correspondence". To ensure that this right is protected employees whose calls are monitored should be given access to a private line over which personal calls can then be made, during their lunch break for example.
Telecoms License obligations – The Service Provision License Private and business use of a telephone system is regulated by certain DTI licenses. These include a similar requirement to that set by the Regulations that "every reasonable effort" to inform parties to a telephone conversation that recording may take place should be made.
Further Reading
Ofcom
Ofcom Website Here
Information Commissioner
ICO Website Here
Department of Business Innovation and Skills
DBIS Website Here
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@printedpens.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 26 Station Road,
Draycott,
Derbyshire.
DE72 3QB
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
